[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
- Our pool! It's here!
- 我们的泳池！它到了！
- Our shelf! It's here!
- 我们的架子！它到了！
- Whoa, that's a lot of face.
- 哇，这么多脸。
- Hey, Karyn, do you have our shelf?
- 嘿，Karyn，你拿到我们的架子了吗？
all: And our pool? - You guys got a pool?
所有人: 还有我们的泳池？ - 你们有泳池？
- Uh, no shelf or pool.
- 呃，没有架子也没有泳池。
all: Aww...
所有人: 啊...
Just a box of cotton balls
只是一盒棉球
and orthopedic shoes.
和矫形鞋。
all: Aww...
- JK.
That's a little delivery humor.
[chuckling] - And we'd be laughing
if we weren't so anxious to swim in our pool--
I mean, you know, build our shelf.
- Thanks, Karyn.
- I'll just see myself out.
- Hey, kids, I know you're dying for a pool,
but isn't it a little early? I mean, it's only spring.
- Nope. This baby's our ticket
- 不。这个宝贝是我们今年夏天让家里成为热门聚集地的门票。
to our house being this year's summer hangout.
让我们的房子成为今年夏天的热门聚集地。
- Yeah, last year, Dooley had a mini zip line at his house,
- 是的，去年，杜利在他家弄了个迷你滑索，
and everyone hung out there for the summer.
整个夏天大家都在那里聚会。
- Literally. - [chuckles]
- 真的是这样。 - [轻笑]
- So that's why we're gonna get our hook in
- 所以我们得抢先一步，
before anyone else gets their hook in.
在别人插手之前先下手为强。
- Speaking of, can we have a pool party here this Saturday?
- 说到这个，我们这周六可以在这里办个泳池派对吗？
- Please say yes, because we've already invited everybody.
- 请说可以，因为我们已经邀请了所有人。
- Sure. all: Yes!
- 当然可以。 大家：太好了！
- Our pool party is gonna be huge.
我们的泳池派对将会非常盛大。
Okay, this is so not huge.
好吧，这绝对不算盛大。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
[愉快的音乐]
- This is the pool you bragged about
这就是你吹嘘的那个
getting such a great deal on?
以超值价格买到的泳池吗？
- Didn't you read the dimensions?
- 你没看尺寸吗？
- Of course! It says it's a 12-foot pool.
- 当然看了！上面写着是12英尺的泳池。
- Actually, it says it's a 12-feet pool.
- 实际上，上面写的是12英尺的泳池。
Apparently, you can only fit 12 feet in it.
显然，你只能在里面放12英尺的东西。
- Or like eight of Mom's feet, am I right?
- 或者放妈妈八个脚那么长，对吧？
[all chuckle]
[大家都笑了]
- But you used to be such a great online shopper.
- 但你以前网购不是挺厉害的吗？
What happened? - Sorry.
怎么回事？ - 对不起。
There was a flash sale, and while I was reading
当时有个限时抢购，我正在看
the details of the return policy,
退货政策的细节，
that little clock in the corner was running out,
角落里的小时钟在倒计时，
and it kept saying, "Act now, act now,"
它一直在说，“现在行动，现在行动，”
so I acted now.
所以我现在就行动了。
- All right, fine.
好吧，好吧。
At least you read the return policy.
至少你读了退货政策。
How is it? - Not good.
怎么样？ - 不太好。
- Okay, well, this tiny pool is a huge problem.
好吧，这个小泳池是个大问题。
Our party's this weekend. - And no pool, no party!
我们的派对这周末就要举行了。 - 没有泳池，就没有派对！
- No party, no people. - No people,
没有派对，就没有人。 - 没有人，
and we're partying at other people's places!
我们就要在别人家里开派对了！
all: What are we gonna do?
大家：我们该怎么办？
- Relax. All we have to do
- 放松。我们只需要
is find a way to make some fast money
找到一种快速赚钱的方法
so we can get that bigger pool.
这样我们就能买那个更大的泳池了。
- Maybe we can do odd jobs around the neighborhood.
- 也许我们可以在社区里做些零工。
- Hey, we could call ourselves the Harper Quad-Jobbers.
- 嘿，我们可以自称是哈珀四人兼职团队。
- Good one. And we could put up flyers.
- 好主意。我们可以贴传单。
And our slogan could be,
我们的口号可以是，
"Eight hands are better than two."
“八只手比两只手强。”
- Not bad. - I like it.
- 不错。 - 我喜欢。
- Eight hands are better than two?
八只手比两只手好？
Nice try, Dawn, but none of us have eight hands.
不错的尝试，Dawn，但我们没人有八只手。
[upbeat music]
- Doh!
哎呀！
Mama jorker!
妈妈工作者！
- Tom, watch your language!
Tom，注意你的言辞！
- Oh, it's the name of the part, Anne.
哦，那是部分的名字，Anne。
I can't get the mama jorker into the...
我无法把妈妈工作者放进...
"lieblein slot."
“lieblein槽。”
- Oh--[scoffs] That's because you have
哦——[嗤之以鼻]那是因为你把方向弄反了。
the directions upside down.
你把方向弄反了。
Why can't you just admit that I am better at this than you?
你为什么就不能承认我在这方面比你强呢？
Here, let me take a stab at it. - Hm.
来，让我试试。 - 嗯。
- [groans] It's stabbing me, Tom.
- [呻吟] 它刺到我了，Tom。
- I'm sorry, Anne, what was it you wanted me to admit?
- 对不起，Anne，你刚才要我承认什么来着？
- [groans] Spleen! Spleen!
- [呻吟] 脾脏！脾脏！
- Oh, oh, sorry. Right here--
- 哦，哦，对不起。就在这儿——
- [gasping]
- [喘气]
- One spleen.
- 一个脾脏。
- No, it's pressing on my spleen!
- 不，是压到我的脾脏了！
- Oh, oh, oh. - [gasps] Oh, thank you.
- 哦，哦，哦。 - [喘气] 哦，谢谢你。
Okay. - Yeah, come on.
好的。 - 是的，来吧。
- Okay. Maybe it's better if we just do it together.
- 好的。也许我们还是一起做比较好。
- I hate you.
- 我讨厌你。
- I hate you too.
- 我也讨厌你。
- [groans] It's just so complicated, Anne!
- [呻吟] 这太复杂了，安妮！
- Oh, we're gonna have to rebuild it, aren't we?
- 哦，我们得重新建造它，对吧？
- Wait a minute... [mumbles]
- 等一下... [咕哝]
Maybe...it isn't so crooked.
也许...它没那么歪。
- Oh, yeah, it looks pretty good.
- 哦，是的，看起来挺好的。
both: Mama jorker!
妈妈乔克！
♪ ♪
- All right, the flyers are up around the neighborhood.
好吧，传单已经在社区周围贴好了。
- And the FaceShack ad is live.
而且FaceShack的广告已经上线了。
- So those calls should come rolling in any second now.
所以那些电话应该随时都会打进来。
- Any second now.
随时都会。
- And... ring.
而且...响了。
- Hold on, you're forgetting something.
等等，你忘了点什么。
Ah-booga, booga, booga, booga, booga, booga, booga.
啊-布加，布加，布加，布加，布加，布加，布加。
- Dicky, you've been doing that since we were three,
迪基，从我们三岁起你就一直在做这个，
and it doesn't work.
而且这招不灵。
[phone rings]
[电话铃响]
- Don't doubt the booga.
- 别怀疑booga的力量。
- Uh, Harper Quad-Jobbers. Eight hands are better than two.
- 呃，哈珀四重工作者。八只手总比两只强。
Are we licensed contractors?
我们是持牌承包商吗？
No.
不是。
Do we have insurance?
我们有保险吗？
No.
没有。
Are we familiar with Italian tiling?
我们对意大利瓷砖熟悉吗？
- Does it have to be Italian? - Does it have to be Italian?
- 非得是意大利的吗？ - 非得是意大利的吗？
No. - Then no.
不。- 那就不用了。
- Yeah, that's a no on the tiling.
- 是的，贴瓷砖的事就算了。
Oh, yes, that we can do.
哦，是的，这个我们可以做。
- What did he want us to do? - Hang up the phone
- 他想要我们做什么？- 挂断电话
and never speak to him again.
并且再也不和他说话。
- Maybe we need to fine-tune our ad
- 也许我们需要调整一下我们的广告
and list what skills we do have.
并列出我们确实拥有的技能。
So, what skills do we have?
那么，我们有什么技能？
Okay, so we've got eating pizza and making lists.
好吧，我们有吃披萨和列清单的能力。
Any other skills?
还有其他技能吗？
[sighs]
[叹气]
Okay, so we've got eating pizza.
好吧，我们有吃披萨。
- Ow, hot. [groans]
- 哎哟，好烫。[呻吟]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
[phone rings] - Oh--
[电话铃响] - 哦--
Harper Quad-Jobbers. Eight hands are better than two.
Harper Quad-Jobbers。八只手比两只手好。
Can we clean rooms? - Yeah.
我们可以打扫房间吗？ - 是的。
- Yes.
- 是的。
And bring in the groceries? - Yes!
还有带进杂货？ - 是的！
- Yes. [chuckles]
- 是的。[轻笑]
And do the dishes? - Yes!
那洗碗呢？ - 是的！
- Yes, that too. - Then do the dishes
- 是的，也包括洗碗。 - 那就洗碗
and all the rest of your chores.
还有你所有的其他家务。
♪ ♪
- [groans] I can't believe it's been a whole day
- [叹气] 我简直不敢相信已经一整天了
and we still haven't gotten one job call.
我们还没接到一个工作电话。
[phone rings] - Ooh, a call.
[电话铃响] - 哦，一个电话。
- Nope, just a timer I set. My turkey melt is ready.
- 不，只是我设的计时器。我的火鸡三明治准备好了。
- You do understand we're in a café...
- 你明白我们现在在一家咖啡馆...
with food...
有食物...
that you can order?
你可以点的那种？
- Duh. I ordered this yesterday.
- 当然。我昨天就点了这个。
I always like to stay a sandwich ahead.
我总是喜欢提前准备一个三明治。
And here's tomorrow's French dip.
这是明天的法式蘸酱三明治。
- There they are, our one-way ticket to Poolville,
- 看，这就是我们通往Poolville的单程票，
population, us.
人口，就是我们。
- We just did a little shopping. - A little?
- 我们只是稍微买了点东西。 - 稍微？
I mean, it looks like you bought the entire pool section.
我的意思是，看起来你把整个泳池区都买下来了。
- I gotta hand it to you, Harpers.
- 我得承认，Harpers。
Pool party, early invites, unseasonably warm temps.
泳池派对，提前邀请，不合季节的温暖天气。
You guys are really on top of your game.
你们真是做得太到位了。
- Always stay a sandwich ahead.
- 总是保持领先一步。
- That's a great metaphor.
- 这比喻真好。
- Sadly, not a metaphor.
- 遗憾的是，这不是比喻。
- We're so excited for your pool party.
- 我们非常期待你们的泳池派对。
- Yeah... [chuckles] Us too.
- 是啊... [轻笑] 我们也是。
I mean, I'm so excited. Even if there wasn't a pool,
我是说，我真的很兴奋。即使没有泳池，
it'd still be the best pool party ever.
这也会是有史以来最好的泳池派对。
Right, guys? [chuckling]
对吧，伙计们？[轻笑]
- No. - Definitely not.
- 不对。 - 绝对不是。
- Ew.
- 咦。
- She's totally kidding. There will definitely
- 她完全是在开玩笑。泳池派对当然会有泳池。
be a pool at the pool party.
- 肯定会有。
- Good, 'cause I already inflated this "floatay"
- 太好了，因为我已经给这个“漂浮物”充好气了，还有这些可爱的小水“玩意儿”。
and cute, tiny water "wangs."
- 快点，伙计们，我也想要一些小水“玩意儿”。
- Come on, guys, I wanna get some tiny, water "wangs" too.
- 是啊，我们走吧。
- Yeah, let's go. - See ya soon.
- 一会儿见。
- See ya.
- 再见。
- Wow. To be honest, I was feeling a little lukewarm
- 哇。老实说，我对整个派对的事情感觉有点不冷不热，
about the whole party thing,
- 但听了他们的话后，我现在很兴奋。
but after hearing them, I'm hyped.
但听了他们的话，我现在很兴奋。
This is gonna be awesome.
这一定会很棒。
- Not if we don't have a pool.
如果我们没有泳池的话，就不行了。
- Oh, man...
哦，天哪...
I knew I was lukewarm for a reason.
我知道我之前感觉一般是有原因的。
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- One, two...
一，二...
- I can't believe I'm doing this.
真不敢相信我正在做这个。
- Just do it. - Three...
- 就去做吧。 - 三...
all: Ah-booga, booga, booga, booga, booga, booga,
大家: Ah-booga, booga, booga, booga, booga, booga,
booga, booga, booga, booga, booga!
- See, I told you it wouldn't work.
- 看吧，我就说这行不通。
- Are you the Harper Quad-Jobbers?
- 你们是Harper Quad-Jobbers吗？
'Cause I could really use some help.
因为我真的很需要帮助。
- We're the Harper Quad-Jobbers! [chuckles]
- 我们是Harper Quad-Jobbers！[轻笑]
- Never doubt the booga. - What do you need us to do?
- 永远不要怀疑booga。 - 你们需要我们做什么？
- Well, I'm gonna be out of town for a couple of days.
- 嗯，我接下来几天要出城。
- Well, we're gonna be in town for a couple of days.
- 嗯，我们接下来几天会在城里。
- Great. I need you to water the plants,
太好了。我需要你给植物浇水，
bring in the mail, take in the trashcans,
收邮件，把垃圾桶拿进来，
take care of my cat.
照顾我的猫。
Oh, and let in and pay the handyman that I hired.
哦，还有让并支付我雇的修理工。
Nothing too hard.
没什么太难的。
Could you start tomorrow? - Absolutely. We'll be there.
你们能从明天开始吗？
- Here's my address.
当然可以。我们会去的。
[lowers voice] I'll put a key under my mat.
这是我的地址。
I know your parents, so I trust you kids.
（压低声音）我会把钥匙放在垫子下面。
- We're on the job.
我认识你们的父母，所以我相信你们这些孩子。
- Cha-ching. - [chuckles]
- 钱来了。 - [轻笑]
- Hold on, wait, we didn't negotiate a price.
- 等等，我们还没谈好价钱。
We don't know how much cha-ching she's cha-chinging us.
我们不知道她要我们付多少钱。
- I'll handle this.
- 我来处理。
They don't call me the Nick-gotiator for nothing.
他们不叫我谈判专家尼克是白叫的。
- Nobody calls you that.
- 没人这么叫你。
- They will after this.
- 他们做完这件事后会的。
- Mmm!
- 嗯！
Ugh. - Did you just lose a tooth?
呃。 - 你刚掉了颗牙吗？
- Nah, it must've been in my pocket,
- 没有，应该是在我口袋里，
but, don't worry, it's not mine.
但别担心，这不是我的。
- [chuckles] - I am worried.
我有点担心。
Whose is it?
那是谁的？
- No idea. I found it this morning.
不知道。我今早发现的。
It's good luck.
这是好运的象征。
- No, a penny is good luck.
不，一分钱才是好运的象征。
- Oh. So what's a tooth?
哦。那牙齿呢？
- Disgusting!
恶心！
- I handled it like a boss.
我处理得像个老板。
Got us each $100.
我们每人赚了100美元。
- That's $400,
- 那是400美元，
and enough to buy our pool.
足够买我们的泳池了。
- What can I say? I'm the Nick-gotiator.
- 我还能说什么呢？我是尼克谈判家。
- Nice job, Nicky. - Nice job who?
- 干得好，尼基。- 干得好，谁？
- Nick-gotiator.
- 尼克谈判家。
- Ah, that feels right, doesn't it?
- 啊，感觉对了，不是吗？
Now everybody.
现在大家。
Come on. Let's hear it.
来吧。让我们听听。
Is that a tooth?
那是一颗牙吗？
- That's mine.
- 那是我的。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Aww, Ms. Monet's kitty is so cute.
- 哦，莫奈小姐的猫咪真可爱。
- I wonder what his name is. - His name is Claws.
- 不知道它叫什么名字。 - 它叫克劳斯。
What a cute name.
多可爱的名字。
You know, normally, cats don't like me,
你知道，通常猫咪都不太喜欢我，
but I've got a good feeling about this little fella.
但我对这个小家伙有种特别的感觉。
- Oh, that must be our payment.
- 哦，那一定是我们的报酬了。
[Claws yowls]
[克劳斯嚎叫]
O-kay.
好吧。
- [whispers] Maybe he doesn't want us to take it
- [低语]也许他不想让我们拿走它
until we've done our work.
直到我们完成工作。
- He's a cat. You don't need to whisper.
- 他是只猫。你不需要低声说话。
[Claws yowls]
[爪子嚎叫]
- Maybe we do.
- 也许我们需要。
- All right, let's just get to work.
- 好吧，让我们开始工作吧。
Mail, trash, cat, plants.
邮件，垃圾，猫，植物。
All done. All we have to do now
都完成了。我们现在要做的
is let in the handyman.
就是让修理工进来。
Claws: Meow!
爪子：喵！
- And pick up the mail.
- 还有，把邮件收一下。
[Claws moans, yowls]
[Claws 呻吟，嚎叫]
Again.
又来了。
- I get the feeling Claws doesn't like us.
- 我感觉Claws不喜欢我们。
- Cats don't pick and choose who they like.
- 猫不会挑人喜欢的。
[Claws yowls] [sweater rips]
[Claws 嚎叫] [毛衣撕裂]
Oops. I think Claws may have caught a thread.
哎呀。我觉得Claws可能勾到了一根线。
- No. - I hardly notice.
- 没有。 - 我几乎没注意到。
- Well, looks like it's time to count the cha-ching,
- 好吧，看起来是时候数数钞票了，
if that's okay with you, Claws. [cat yowls]
如果你不介意的话，Claws。[猫嚎叫]
- You don't need to ask the cat's permission.
你不必征求猫的意见。
[Claws yowls] [sweater rips]
[爪子喵喵叫][毛衣撕裂]
Oh, dear...
哦，天哪...
I think Claws may have nicked a button.
我觉得爪子可能弄掉了一个扣子。
- No. - All good.
- 不是。- 都好。
- Button's fine.
- 扣子没事。
Okay, let's open this thing.
好的，我们打开这个吧。
Pool party, here we come.
泳池派对，我们来了。
$100? Where's the rest?
100美元？剩下的呢？
- There's supposed to be $400 in there.
- 应该有400美元在里面。
- Yeah, that's what I negotiated, $400.
- 是的，我谈的是400美元。
Ms. Monet said she'd give all of us $100.
莫奈女士说她会给我们每个人100美元。
- All of us...
- 我们所有人...
or each of us?
还是我们每个人？
- What's the difference? - $300!
- 有什么区别？ - 300美元！
All means all of us together.
所有意味着我们所有人加起来。
Each meant we would each get $100.
每个意味着我们每个人会得到100美元。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Now we have to find out a way to earn the extra $300
- 现在我们得想办法赚到额外300美元
we need for our pool.
我们需要为我们的游泳池。
- So much for my lucky tooth. [spits]
- 我的幸运牙也没带来好运。[吐出]
- You had that in your mouth?
- 你嘴里含着那个？
- Yeah. Where else would you keep a tooth?
- 对啊。不然你牙齿放哪儿？
- But it's not your tooth.
- 但那不是你的牙。
- That doesn't mean it's not welcome.
- 那并不意味着它不受欢迎。
- Okay, can we please forget about the tooth?
- 好吧，我们能不能别再提那颗牙了？
We need to find a way to make the extra money.
我们需要找到赚取额外钱的方法。
We need opportunity to come knocking.
我们需要机会来敲门。
[knocking on door]
[敲门声]
- Whoa, and we didn't even have to booga.
- 哇，我们甚至都不用跳布加舞。
- I did a silent booga.
我做了个无声的booga。
- Hey, I'm Aaron.
嘿，我是Aaron。
Ms. Monet hired me to build a shelf.
Monet女士雇我来建一个架子。
- Oh, yeah. Box is right there,
哦，对了。箱子就在那儿，
and money is in the envelope.
钱在信封里。
[cat yowls] - Oh--
哦——
- By the way, the cat won't pay you until you finish your job.
顺便说一下，猫不会付你钱直到你完成工作。
- Cat? I didn't know she had a cat.
猫？我不知道她有猫。
[sneezes]
阿嚏！
I am severely allergic to cats.
我对猫严重过敏。
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
No amount of money is worth...
多少钱都不值得……
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
That.
那样。
- Oh, that's a shame.
哦，那真是可惜。
Just out of curiosity,
只是出于好奇，
how much is Ms. Monet paying you?
莫奈女士付给你多少钱？
- $300.
300美元。
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
- Uh, well, I mean, we could do you a solid
呃，我是说，我们可以帮你个忙
and build that shelf for you.
并且帮你建那个架子。
- [wheezing] Whatever.
- [喘息声] 随便吧。
[strained] My throat's closing.
[吃力] 我的喉咙要闭上了。
- [whispers] Yes!
- [低语] 太好了！
- [sneezes] - Whoa!
- [打喷嚏] - 哇！
- Dawn, what did you do?
- 道恩，你做了什么？
- I just got us 300 bucks.
- 我刚为我们赚了300美元。
- But we've never built a shelf before.
- 但我们从未建过架子。
- [scoffs] Mom and Dad built one.
- [嗤之以鼻] 爸爸妈妈建过一个。
I mean, how hard could it be?
我是说，能有多难？
[Claws yowls]
[爪子喵叫]
Okay, but we gotta take care of that cat first.
好吧，但我们得先照顾那只猫。
- Well, I think it's pretty obvious
- 嗯，我认为这很明显
he likes me best, so...
他最喜欢我，所以...
[cat yowls]
[猫喵叫]
Here, Clawsy, Clawsy, Clawsy!
过来，Clawsy，Clawsy，Clawsy！
- Harper Quad-Jobbers got the job done.
- Harper Quad-Jobbers完成了任务。
- I am very proud of us.
- 我为我们感到非常骄傲。
- We're gonna have the coolest pool party ever.
- 我们将举办有史以来最酷的泳池派对。
- Ricky, we're done!
- Ricky，我们完成了！
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
- That cat... [panting]
- 那只猫... [喘气]
is a monster.
是个怪物。
- Why didn't you yell for help?
- 你为什么不喊救命？
- 'Cause he shoved a sock in my mouth.
- 因为他把一只袜子塞进了我嘴里。
- He did? - You think that's bad?
- 他真的做了？ - 你觉得这很糟糕吗？
Look what else he did.
看看他还做了什么。
- The cat can write?
- 那只猫会写字？
- No...
- 不...
[whispers] he made me do it.
[低语] 是他逼我做的。
- How did you know what to write?
- 你怎么知道要写什么？
- It was in his eyes.
- 他的眼神告诉了我。
Can we go now?
我们现在可以走了吗？
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- I am proud of us, Anne. - Me too.
- 我为我们感到骄傲，安妮。 - 我也是。
You know, I can't wait to put our beautiful collectibles
你知道吗，我迫不及待要在13年后展示我们的美丽收藏品了。
out on display after 13 years.
- 哈哈哈哈。 - [叹气] 好吧。
- Ha-ha-ha-ha. - [exhales] Okay.
[物体碰撞声] 哎呀，我们忘了一个部分。
[object clatters] Uh-oh. We forgot a part.
- 呃，只是个弹簧片。
- Eh, it's just a fling-flange.
- 现在，在按下购买我们尺寸合适的泳池之前，进行仪式性的手指抬起，
- And now, the ceremonial finger raise,
- 现在，进行仪式性的手指抬起，
before I press "purchase" on our appropriately sized pool.
在我按下购买我们合适尺寸的泳池之前。
[cash register dings] - Yes!
叮！ - 太好了！
- You know what, I'm gonna have half of
- 你知道吗，为了庆祝，我明天要吃半个金枪鱼三明治。
tomorrow's tuna sandwich to celebrate.
[物体叮当声] - 那是什么声音？
[object clinks] - What's that?
- 哎呀，我们忘记了一个零件。
- Uh-oh, we forgot a piece.
- 呃，那只是个弹簧片。
- Eh, it's just a fling-flange.
[吱吱声] - 那吱吱声是什么？
[creaking] - What's that creaking noise?
[吱吱声继续]
[creaking continues]
- 等等，那声音是从架子那边传来的吗？
- Wait, is that sound coming from the shelf?
- 等等，那个声音是从架子那边传来的吗？
[items clatter]
[物品碰撞声]
Oh! Ohh...
哦！哦...
- Huh...
- 嗯...
I guess we did need this fling-flange.
看来我们确实需要那个飞翼法兰。
- Ugh, Tom, help me. - Oh!
- 呃，汤姆，帮帮我。 - 哦！
- You don't think, because we left out a fling-flange,
- 你不会觉得，因为我们少了一个飞翼法兰，
Ms. Monet's shelf is gonna collapse too?
莫奈女士的架子也会塌掉吧？
all: Nah.
大家: 不会。
all: Yeah!
大家: 是的！
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Uh, guys...
- 呃，伙计们...
how'd all this stuff get on these shelves?
这些东西是怎么放到这些架子上的？
- I put it there!
- 我放的！
- [gasps] Mrs. Monet...
- [吸气声] 莫奈夫人...
- What are you doing here? - I came back early.
- 你在这里做什么？ - 我提前回来了。
What are you kids doing here?
你们这些孩子在这里做什么？
Looks like you finished all your work for the day.
看起来你们今天的工作都完成了。
- [chuckles] - Oh... uh...
- [轻笑] - 哦... 呃...
Ricky just really wanted to see Claws.
Ricky只是真的很想见Claws。
- Ha, yeah, they really bonded. Isn't that right, Ricky?
哈，是的，他们真的建立了深厚的联系。对吧，Ricky？
- Yep, he really left his mark on me.
是的，他真的在我身上留下了他的印记。
- Oh, well, he obviously loves you.
哦，好吧，他显然很爱你。
Look at the way he's staring at you.
看看他盯着你的样子。
- Yep. His eyes say so much.
是的。他的眼睛说了很多。
- Mm-hm.
嗯哼。
- So, Ms. Monet...
那么，Monet女士...
what's with all the new stuff on the shelf?
架子上所有的新东西是怎么回事？
- I got it all on my trip.
这些都是我在旅行中买的。
I'm a big blown glass collector.
It's so beautiful,
and yet so fragile.
- Awesome. - Fancy!
- Expensive? - Extremely.
- Well, don't you think something so beautiful
and fragile should go somewhere, oh, I don't know,
anywhere but the shelf?
- No, this is perfect to display them.
That's why I had this shelf built.
[wood creaks]
[木头吱嘎声]
What's that noise?
那是什么声音？
- That's just my... stomach.
- 那只是我的... 肚子。
- Yeah! Some people's growl.
- 是的！有些人的肚子会咕噜叫。
His...
他的...
does that.
会这样。
- Oh, well, if you're hungry, I've got a pot of soup.
- 哦，好吧，如果你饿了，我有一锅汤。
Would you like some? It's borscht.
你想来点吗？是罗宋汤。
- What's borscht?
- 罗宋汤是什么？
- It is a broth made of beets, and it's served cold.
- 它是一种用甜菜根做的汤，通常是冷的。
- It's delicious!
太好吃了！
- Yum. [chuckles]
好吃。[轻笑]
Will you excuse us for one second?
请你们稍等一下好吗？
- [nervous chuckle]
[紧张的笑]
- [whispers] Are you guys thinking what I'm thinking?
[低声]你们是不是在想我正在想的事情？
- How Ricky looks terrified?
Ricky看起来很害怕吗？
- No. That when she gets the soup,
不是。当她拿到汤的时候，
we can put the fling-flange in the hole.
我们可以在洞里放上那个弹簧装置。
- I'll go help her with the borscht,
我去帮她拿罗宋汤，
and I'll give you guys the signal
我会给你们信号
once she's headed back in. - Okay, what's the signal?
一旦她回来。 - 好的，信号是什么？
- "Who's ready for borscht?" - I am, but what's the signal?
- “谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？” - 我准备好了，但信号是什么？
- "Who's ready for borscht?"
- “谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？”
- I told you. I am. But what's the signal?
- 我告诉过你了。我准备好了。但信号是什么？
- "Who's ready for borscht?"
- “谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？”
- You know what, let's just make that the signal,
- 你知道吗，我们就把那个当作信号吧，
because I am really ready for borscht.
因为我真的准备好喝罗宋汤了。
- Good idea!
- 好主意！
Mrs. Monet, we would love to stay.
莫奈夫人，我们很愿意留下来。
How about I give you a hand in the kitchen?
我来帮你在厨房里忙怎么样？
- Oh, why, thank you, young man.
哦，为什么，谢谢你，年轻人。
- [whispers] Okay, Dicky, give me the fling-flange.
好的，迪基，把那个飞翼装置给我。
- [grunts] - [sniffing]
哼哼
Ew, why does it smell like tuna?
哎呀，为什么闻起来像金枪鱼？
- For the same reason my sandwich
因为我的三明治
smells like fling-flange.
闻起来像飞翼装置。
- It's getting worse. - What, the creaking?
情况越来越糟。
- No, the rage in his eyes.
什么，是吱吱声吗？
[wood creaking] - And the shelf.
不，是他眼中的愤怒。
Oh--I found the hole for the fling-flange.
哦——我找到了飞翼装置的孔。
- Who's ready for borscht? Who's ready for borscht?
- 谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？
Who's ready for borscht? - Who's ready for borscht?
谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？ - 谁准备好喝罗宋汤了？
- She knows the signal.
- 她知道信号。
- I was only able to get the fling-flange halfway in.
- 我只能把fling-flange插进去一半。
- I hope it works.
- 希望它能起作用。
- Thank you, Mrs. Monet.
- 谢谢你，莫奈太太。
Looks delicious. [chuckles]
看起来很美味。[轻笑]
- [sniffs] Uh, it's not.
- [嗅] 呃，不是的。
- Oh, you're right. I forgot the sour cream!
- 哦，你说得对。我忘了加酸奶油！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Ha. Look at Claws.
哈，看看Claws。
He's licking the fling-flange.
他在舔那个飞盘。
- Yeah, maybe because it's covered in tuna juice.
是啊，可能是因为上面沾了金枪鱼汁。
- Oh. Right.
哦，对。
- He's gonna knock it out.
他要把那东西弄下来了。
Shoo! Shoo, shoo, shoo! [cat yowls]
去！去，去，去！[猫叫]
[gasps] Oh, no, he took the fling-flange.
哎呀，不好，他把飞盘拿走了。
[wood creaks] - It's about to go.
[木头吱嘎声] - 马上就要掉了。
- We gotta do something. - Wait, don't worry.
我们得做点什么。 - 等等，别担心。
That slot is the same size as my lucky tooth.
那个槽的大小和我幸运的牙齿一样。
[slow motion whoosh]
[慢动作嗖嗖声]
- Yeeeees!
- 耶！
all: No!
所有人: 不！
[creaking]
[吱吱声]
[glass shatters]
[玻璃破碎声]
- My blown glass!
- 我的吹制玻璃！
- This could not have gone worse.
- 这不可能更糟糕了。
[Claws growls]
[爪子咆哮]
[slow motion] Noooo!
[慢动作] 不！
♪ ♪
- So, we had to give all of our bookshelf money back
所以我们不得不把买书架的钱都退回去
and had to cancel the order for our full-size pool.
还取消了全尺寸游泳池的订单。
all: Aww... - But don't worry,
哎呀……
our parents hired the Harper Quad-Jobbers
但是别担心
to build a shelving unit for them.
我们的父母请了哈珀四份工来为他们搭建架子。
- And this time, we used all the pieces.
这次我们用上了所有的零件。
- And our parents paid us
而且我们的父母通过给我们买那个全尺寸游泳池来支付我们。
by buying us that full-size pool.
耶！
all: Yay! - So everything worked out
所以一切都完美解决了。
perfectly for everyone. - Did it?
是吗？
Did it really?
真的吗？
- So, can we go swimming or not?
- 那我们可以去游泳了吗？
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- 是的！
- Sweet!
- 太好了！
- Marco...
马可...
Marco...
- Yeah, I think adult swim is over.
- 是的，我想成人游泳时间结束了。
- Let's kick your dad out of the pool.
- 我们把爸爸赶出泳池吧。
- Yeah. [laughter]
- 是的。
- Oh--whoa! [snow whooshing]
- 哦——哇！
- It's snowing?
- 下雪了？
- How did the weather change so quickly?
- 天气怎么变得这么快？
- Mother nature! - [shudders]
- 大自然的力量！
- Maybe it was a little early to have a pool party.
- 可能开泳池派对有点太早了。
- How is your dad standing it out there?
- 你爸怎么受得了外面？
- C-come on...in.
- 快进来...
The...water's great!
- 水...水很棒！
- Pizza party?
- 披萨派对？
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- 对！
- ♪♪
-
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ 耶耶，耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪